[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":491876,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":499220,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":16284,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":515507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":32700,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":548210,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":9711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":557924,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1899,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":559826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":14131,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":573959,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":23961,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":597923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":603214,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1323,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":604540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the  sum is 6  or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6692,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":611235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":21345,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":632584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4290,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":636878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":3408,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":640289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":46323,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":686615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":2159,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":688776,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Rem ember, t o perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4219,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":692998,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1387,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":694388,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4889,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":699279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":700289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3668,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":703960,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":704971,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":11006,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":715981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</su b>). Sim ilarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":41160,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":757144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":92876,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":850025,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":14664,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":864691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br / > (Remem ber, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":869141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2484,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":871628,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5611,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":877243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1538,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":878784,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2805,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":881593,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1188,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":882784,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of  0 under  +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3100,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":885888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4820,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":890711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 because using +6, you have to subtract 6 to get 0. ","response_history":["It seems that it's jus ","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 to ","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 to","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 t","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 ","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 e","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 because using +6, you have to subract ","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 because using +6, you have to subract","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 because using +6, you have to subrac","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 because using +6, you have to subra","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 because using +6, you have to subr","It seems that it's just whichever number will equal 6 becau se using  +6, you have to subtract 6 to get 0. "],"rt":145793,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1036507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":99209,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1135720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub> 6</sub>  1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":29044,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1164766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7500,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1172270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just  3.","rt":3536,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1175810,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2230,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1178044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":7403,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1185450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2193,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1187647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1439,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1189089,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1192457,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1687,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1194149,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Most of the non generators are even num bers(sav e for 0 which has no value and 3) while all the generators are odd numbers. With the generators you can use both of them to get to the value of 6, but you cannot do so for the non generators.","response_history":["Most of the non generators are even nym","Most of the non generators are even ny","Most of the non generators are even numbers(save for 0 which has no value and 3) while all the generatos","Most of the non generators are even numbers(save for 0 which has no value and 3) while all the generators are odd numbers. WHich","Most of the non generators are even numbers(save for 0 which has no value and 3) while all the generators are odd numbers. WHic","Most of the non generators are even numbers(save for 0 which has no value and 3) while all the generators are odd numbers. WHi","Most of the non generators are even numbers(save for 0 which has no value and 3) while all the generators are odd numbers. WH","Most of the non generators are even numbers(save for 0 which has no  value a nd 3) while all the generators are odd numbers. With the generators you can use both of them to get to the value of 6, but you cannot do so for the non generators."],"rt":131564,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1325715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10768,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1336487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4395,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1340884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1418,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1342306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1347587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1355380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":" free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3473,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1358856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1361153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4697,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1365853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5, because 4+1 is less than 9 so I would just add th em like  normal.","response_history":["5, because 4+1 is less than 9 so I would just add them like normal."],"rt":19286,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1385142,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3, because 8+4 is greater than 9, so I need to subtract 9 from the total.","response_history":["3, n","3, because 8+4 is greater than 9, so I need to subtract 9 from the total."],"rt":27246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1412392,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 because anything that equals 9 in an equation using +9 is going to be 0","response_history":[" 0 becaus e anything that equals 9 is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9  is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 i is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in  is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in a is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an  is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an e is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an eq is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equ is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equa is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equati is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equatio is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equation is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equation  is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an eq uation u  is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equation usi is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equation usin is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equation using  is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equation using + is going to be 0","0 because anything that equals 9 in an equation using +9 is going to be 0"],"rt":109509,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1521903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":12496,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1534402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":5392,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1539797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, because 6+3=9 and anything equal to or greater than 9 means that we subtract 9 and in this case we get 0","response_history":["6, because 6+3=9 and anything equal to or greater than 9 b","6, because 6+3=9 and anything equal to or greater than 9 means that we subtract 9 and in this case we get 0"],"rt":31746,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1571547,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because you can't use it with every number to get to 9","response_history":["N o because you can't use it with every number to get to 9"],"rt":49188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1620738,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because you can't use it with any number to get to 9","response_history":["No, because you can't use it with any u","No, because you can't use it with any number to get to 9"],"rt":20300,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1641042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because you can use it with any number to get to 9","response_history":["Yes because you can use it with any number to get to  9"],"rt":14763,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1655809,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because you are unable to use it with any number to reach the number 9","response_history":["No, because you are unable to use it with any number to reach the nyum","No, because you are unable to use it with any number to reach the nyu","No, because you are unable to use it with any number to reach the ny","No, because you are unable to use it with any number to reach the number 9"],"rt":21125,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1676936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could b e any ot her counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":14996,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1691935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +8(n)7=0","response_history":["1+","1 +_n x= >","1 +_n x= <or=","1 +_n x= <or","1 +_n x= <o","1 +_n x= <","1 +_n x= ","1 +_n x=","1 +_n x","1 +_n ","1 +_n","1 +_","1 +6","1 +8(n)7=0"],"rt":193740,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1885678,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to +n","response_history":["x +n = (","x +n = ","x +n =","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inervse wo","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inervse w","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inervse ","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inervse","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inervs","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inerv","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The iner","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The ine","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to th echos","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to th echo","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to th ech","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to th ec","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to th e","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to th ","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would  be equa l to th","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to t","x +n y= (x+y) -n. The inverse would be whatever number plus x would be equal to +n"],"rt":104231,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1989913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator.","response_history":["I'm not really sure. I didn't k","I'm not really sure. I d idn't no tice a full on pattern, i","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1 ","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For =6,","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For =6","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact t hat most  generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For =","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For +6, however I did notice that numbers that normal would make that number were non generators.","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For +6, ho wever I  did notice that numbers that normal would make that number were non generators (ex. 2x2x2=6, 3x2-","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For +6, however I did notice that numbers that normal would make that number were non generators (ex. 2x2x2=6, 3x2=6 and","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For +6, however I did notice that numbers that normal would make that number were non generators (ex. 2x 2x2=6, 3 x2=6 an","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For +6, however I did notice that numbers that normal would make that number were non generators (ex. 2x2x2=6, 3x2=6 a","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some things that stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator. For +6, however I did notice that numbers that normal would make that number were non generators (ex. 2x2x2=6, 3x2=6 ","I'm not really sure. I didn't notice a full on pattern, I did notice some th ings tha t stood out such as the fact that most generators appeared to be odd numbers(1, 5 for +6), however 3 was a non generator so that did not fit perfectly. I also noticed that most non generators were even numbers (2, 4) though 3 was a non generator."],"rt":147068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2136983,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["True","False"],"rt":11683,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2148670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":4303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2152976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":9498,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2162477,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples/divisors of 6 or any numbers related to it.","response_history":["I think it might be true because in the case of +6,","I think it might be true because in the case of +6- 2,","I think it might be true because in the case of +6- 2","I think it might be true because in the case of +6- ","I think it might be true because in the case of +6-","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4 a","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4 ","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And a","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples of o","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples of ","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples of","I think it might be true because in the case  of +6, 2 ,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples o","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples ","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples or","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples o","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1 ,5) were  not multiples ","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples/divisors of 6 or any nyum","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples/divisors of 6 or any nyu","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples/divisors of 6 or any nyumb","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were n ot multi ples/divisors of 6 or any nyum","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples/divisors of 6 or any nyu","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples/divisors of 6 or any ny","I think it might be true because in the case of +6, 2,4, and 3 were not generators. And each of those numbers are multiples/divisors of 6 itself or the other non generators while the generator numbers(1,5) were not multiples/divisors of 6 or any numbers related to it."],"rt":105172,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2267651,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under + <sub>n</ sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":25898,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2293553,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and they were the inverse of each other.","response_history":["In the","In th","In t","In ","In","I","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they  are both  the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 3 w","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 3 ","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 3","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and those were non generators of =6.","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and those were non generators of =6","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and those were non generators of =","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each  other.  However, 2 and 4 were non generators and those were non generators of ","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and those were non generators of","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and those were non generators o","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and those were non generators ","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and those were non generators.","I chose sometimes because in the case of +6, 1 and 5 were generators and they are both the inverse of each other. However, 2 and 4 were non generators and they were the inverse  of each  other."],"rt":67464,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2361019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":27461,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2388485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2033,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2390521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"23","response_history":["23"],"rt":2688,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2393212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2396049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra 2","response_history":["ALgreba ","ALgreba","ALgreb","ALgre","ALgr","ALg","AL","Algebra 2"],"rt":10207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2406259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":29447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2435710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often o r recent ly","response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":18791,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2454505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"rt":9583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2464091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3399,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2467494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy th is HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":1938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2469436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2008,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2471448,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4538,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2475989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you  use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5252,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2481245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Pretty fun. There were some parts that I feel I could've used a bit more explaining/examples for, but all in all I think I grasped the main point.","response_history":["Pretty fun. There were some parts that I feel I could've used a bit more explaining.","Pretty fun. There were some parts that I feel I could've used a bit more explaining/examples for, but all in all I think I got the ","Pretty fun. There were some parts that I feel I could've used a bit more explaining/examples for, but all in all I think I g","Pretty fun. There were some parts that I feel I could've  used a b it more explaining/examples for, but all in all I think I grasped the main point."],"rt":33219,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2514467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]